<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<item>
		<title>AND THE WINNER IS</title>
		<link>http://www.frontiersupport.co.uk/blog/and-the-winner-is</link>
		<description>We are delighted to have been selected as a finalist of the 2016 National Learning Disabilities Awards. These awards celebrate excellence in the support for people with learning disabilities and aim to pay tribute to those individuals or organisation who excel in providing quality care.The National Learning Disabilities Awards are organised by Care Talk and supported by the Department of Health, Association of Directors of Adult Social Services (ADASS), Social Care Institute for Excellence (SCIE) and Skills for Care and Voluntary Organisations Disability Group (VODG). Our CEO, Denise Doggett, attended an interview with the other finalists on 25th May and the winners will be announced at a national ceremony at the ICC in Birmingham on 14th July.Denise said: “We aim help our clients to live active and socially inclusive lives incorporating routines, hobbies and learning of their choosing. These might include life skills such as managing their own money, cooking and doing their food shopping or perhaps taking part in a weekly club or class or even getting to the cinema.“We love what we do and have around 130 committed staff who work really hard to make a difference to people’s lives so it’s fantastic to have been recognised for our work in this arena.”Fingers crossed for 14th July!!</description>
		<pubDate>2016-05-31 07:57:48</pubDate>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>FRONTIER HOSTS EUROPEAN CONFERENCE</title>
		<link>http://www.frontiersupport.co.uk/blog/frontier-hosts-european-conference</link>
		<description>We were delighted to work in partnership with Outside In Pathways to play host to the Sharing European Knowledge on Autism (SEKA) conference in Croydon in May 2016. SEKA comprises organisations from Austria, Northern Ireland, Romania, Turkey and the United Kingdom. Each organisation shares their knowledge and expertise in Autism.
The SEKA project aims to help families to better understand their children and autism. The two-year study will involve interviews with over 100 families in the five member regions. These interviews will be analysed by experts and the results will be presented at an international conference in Turkey in 2017.
The information gathered will be used to create training courses and resources for parents of children with Autism and these will cover issues such as education, health, social rights and entitlements, legal rights, and psychosocial support.
SEKA will publish materials and resources in four languages across the European member states and the findings will be used by educators, healthcare professionals, policymakers and families.
The Croydon conference was a lively and productive event and we look forward to the next conference which will be hosted by our colleagues in Northern Ireland.</description>
		<pubDate>2016-06-09 09:21:34</pubDate>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>It’s the taking part that counts</title>
		<link>http://www.frontiersupport.co.uk/blog/It-the-taking-part-that-counts</link>
		<description>A group of Frontier staff and clients enjoyed a fantastic overnight stay in Birmingham for the Finals of the 2016 National Learning Disabilities Awards.
We were extremely excited to have been shortlisted as the awards celebrate excellence in the support of people with learning disabilities and aim to pay tribute to those individuals or organisation who excel in providing quality care.
The National Learning Disabilities Awards are organised by Care Talk and supported by the Department of Health, Association of Directors of Adult Social Services (ADASS), Social Care Institute for Excellence (SCIE) and Skills for Care and Voluntary Organisations Disability Group (VODG).
Unfortunately, we didn’t on this occasion but a great time was had by all and it was fantastic to be part of the finals and to have our work with our clients recognised.</description>
		<pubDate>2016-07-26 05:52:32</pubDate>
	</item>
<item><title>Frontier Support Hits Double Figures</title><link>http://192.168.100.97/sagar/frontier/pro/blog/frontier-support-hits-double-figures</link><description>A great evening was enjoyed by around 100 staff, clients and families at the Croydon Conference Centre on Saturday 13th August to celebrate Frontier Support&rsquo;s 10th birthday.&nbsp; Guests were treated to a buffet meal followed by an evening of dancing and everyone left with a gift.&nbsp;&#13;
Denise Doggett, CEO of Frontier Support, said: &ldquo;We&rsquo;re so proud of what we&rsquo;ve achieved over the past ten years and wanted, in the first instance, to celebrate the company&rsquo;s birthday with the people who make it all possible &ndash; our clients, their families and our staff.&nbsp; Some of our clients have been with us for many years and we&rsquo;ve seen them develop and grow with us so it was lovely to share the evening with them&rdquo;.</description><pubDate>2016-08-23 04:31:06</pubDate></item></channel>
</rss>
